{
    "subject": "resource/Kofi_Annan",
    "predicate": "ontology/almaMater",
    "object": "resource/Macalester_College",
    "human_readable": "Kofi Annan attended Macalester College.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9865574240684509,
            "question": "Was Kofi Annan a student at Macalester College?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9858229756355286,
            "question": "Did Kofi Annan study at Macalester College?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9529058337211609,
            "question": "Name the college that Kofi Annan attended."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.905039370059967,
            "question": "Where did Kofi Annan attend college?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8727412223815918,
            "question": "What is the name of the college Kofi Annan attended?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8443850874900818,
            "question": "To which college did Kofi Annan go?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7671855688095093,
            "question": "Which college did Kofi Annan graduate from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.738099992275238,
            "question": "In what college did Kofi Annan receive his education?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6221176981925964,
            "question": "What educational institution is Kofi Annan linked to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48991015553474426,
            "question": "What institution of higher learning was Kofi Annan associated with?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Kofi Annan attended Macalester College.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7731_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What educational institution is Kofi Annan linked to?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7731_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what college did Kofi Annan receive his education?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7731_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which college did Kofi Annan graduate from?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7731_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7731_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7731_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7731_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7731_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7731_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7731_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7731_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7731_76.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7731_95.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7731_99.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the structured JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide multiple instances of information that confirms Kofi Annan attended Macalester College."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide multiple references to Kofi Annan's attendance at Macalester College, thus supporting the statement that Kofi Annan attended Macalester College."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}